mobiletest.me 2018-05-14

# MobileTest.me - Test your mobile sites and responsive web designs

## Privacy policy & cookies

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for MobileTest.me This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

#### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You can modify your personal information through the '[My Account](http://mobiletest.me/account)' page. 

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

We do not collect sensitive information other than the information needed for issuing invoices. We will only collect this information if you explicitly request us to issue an invoice (during payment). 

We do not collect or store your credit card data. We use third parties to process payments. Specifically [BrainTree](https://www.braintreepayments.com/) and [Paypal](https://www.paypal.com/). 

Your passwords are encrypted and are not available even to us. This means that we can not and never will send you your password. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to any personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

#### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. 

#### Registration

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the [Sign up](http://mobiletest.me/user/signup) form. During registration a user is required to give an email address. This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

#### Orders

We request information from you on our order form. To become a subscriber, you must provide contact information (like name and billing address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you. 

We only store your contact information for the purpose of issuing invoices. We do not store your credit card or other financial information. See section 'Security' above. 

#### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. 

Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

For any questions you might have about your data and our use of it, please use the [Contact](http://mobiletest.me/page/contact) form or the [Feedback](http://mobiletest.me/messages) page from within the app
